MAARTJE OOSTVOGELS

7 Blackdown Hall | Leamington Spa, CV32 6RD | 07718377087 | moostvogels@hotmail.com



SUMMARY

Professional with extensive experience as a regional manager. Comfortable working with people from different backgrounds and a proven ability to motivate staff on an individual and team level. Excellent commercial approach to solving problems to meet business objectives and a track record for effective strategies when implementing and developing systems.

EXPERIENCE

Operations Manager, The Steamhouse

July 2016 – Present

Leamington Spa, United Kingdom

- Facilitated the implementation and advancement of all in store and back of house procedures, policies and systems.
- Created HR and recruitment strategies which improved job satisfaction and significantly decreased staff turnover and sickness.
- Identified business expansion opportunities and managed initial set up of Worcester and Redditch high turnover stores.
- Responsible for recruitment, initial training and ongoing development of all staff.
- Responsible for all stores and mobile units regarding store operations, maintenance, stock control and order processing.
- Carrying out regular site visits to provide in store support.
- Ensuring product quality and customer service standards are upheld across stores.
- Ensuring compliance to all Environmental Health & Safety goals and objectives.

Senior Customer Consultant, The Body Shop

October 2015 – July 2016

Leamington Spa, United Kingdom

- Initial setup and close of designated unit, providing customers with excellent customer service throughout the day.
- Helping customers choose products suitable to their needs.
- Proactively seek to help the team achieve its daily sales goals.
- Monitoring store and staff performance.

Warwick, United Kingdom

- Initial setup and close down of designated unit, providing customers with excellent customer service throughout the day, ensure stocks are continuously filled up with merchandise.
- Serving dishes during weddings, corporate events and private parties to the standards required.
- Answering guest gueries in a polite and helpful manner.
- Looking after guests with special dietary requirements/allergies.

HR & Recruitment Coordinator, Sterksen IT Recruitment

July 2014 – March 2015

Breda, The Netherlands

- Working with a small team of recruiters and acting as liaison between Sterksen and clients to organize recruitment activities.
- Responsible for upkeep of personnel files.
- Managed administration regarding employees, contractors and interim assignments.
- Updated recruitment process documents and processes.

HR & Recruitment Coordinator, Tesla Motors

April 2013 – July 2014

Tilburg, The Netherlands

- An administrative role, helping to co-ordinate and facilitate the organization of recruitment activities for the local Tesla assembly.
- Responsible for generating contracts, liaising with managers regarding new hires, onboarding and introducing new employees.
- First point of contact for queries regarding holiday policy, Dutch healthcare and employee stock plan.

Coach/Integration Consultant, Alexander Calder November 2010 – April 2013

Tilburg, The Netherlands

- Responsible for providing group training involving empowerment, work ethics, job application processes, building a resume, etc.
- Helped individuals identify suitable education and employment.
- Maintained individual progress reports with regard to personal progression.

EDUCATION

Fontys University of Human Resources Management & Psychology – Tilburg, The Netherlands – Bachelor or Human Resource Management

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Fluent in spoken and written English
- Fluent in spoken and written Dutch
- Basic level of spoken and written German
- Computing Skills: Word, MS Access, Excel, Adobe Photoshop
- Full, clean driving license